<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2025-05-22T19:54:33-04:00</updated><id>https://seth.rip/seth.rip/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Seth’s Mind</title><subtitle>A place for my head.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">i told you once</title><link href="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/itoldyou/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="i told you once" /><published>2025-05-22T19:44:00-04:00</published><updated>2025-05-22T19:44:00-04:00</updated><id>https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/itoldyou</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/itoldyou/"><![CDATA[<p>i told you once that i need you.</p>

<p>if i told you everything, would you think im crazy?
if you’ve seen everywhere i’ve been wou’</p>]]></content><author><name>[&quot;sathe&quot;]</name></author><category term="chatting" /><category term="unknown" /><category term="confusion" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[i told you once that i need you.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">You’re still thinking of me.</title><link href="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/stillthinking/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="You’re still thinking of me." /><published>2025-03-29T22:35:00-04:00</published><updated>2025-03-29T22:35:00-04:00</updated><id>https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/stillthinking</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/stillthinking/"><![CDATA[<p>So you’re still thinking of me. Just like I know you would.</p>

<p>I cannot give you everything.</p>

<p>You know I wish I could.</p>

<p>I’m too caught up in this.</p>

<p>We still have love to give.</p>

<p>Would you do it all again? I know I would… right?</p>

<p>What would I change? I’d go back.</p>

<p>I would <em>maybe</em> change it all…. My future is on the rocks as of currently. Many paths I can take, not sure which is the right one.</p>

<p>Best of all, not sure even who my friends are anymore. Everything is just a blur. I guess that’s why they call me Mr. Worldwide.</p>

<p><strong>Who are my friends? If you are my friend, DM me 10893.</strong></p>

<p>But other than that, anything is possible, yes?</p>

<p>I’ve started another project, though my time management / motivation has yet to improve signifigantly. Infact, I’d say my studying has decreased by, maybe, all.</p>

<p>I need help deciding my future.</p>

<p>I may not be the worst or the best…</p>

<p>So, what the actual fuck do I do with myself???</p>

<p>I need a shot of memories. a shot of vodka. im too scatter brained. there’s multiple people inside me i feel. sometimes i wanna do something, but other times I want to do the COMPLETE OPPOSITE. I can never choose.</p>]]></content><author><name>[&quot;seth&quot;, &quot;deathrow&quot;]</name></author><category term="chatting" /><category term="unknown" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[So you’re still thinking of me. Just like I know you would.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">the final end.</title><link href="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/thelastdays/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="the final end." /><published>2024-12-11T17:03:00-05:00</published><updated>2024-12-11T17:03:00-05:00</updated><id>https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/thelastdays</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/thelastdays/"><![CDATA[<p>the final days. i see a phsyciatrist at the end of the month. too far away. i hav eto move out of my room soon. i will miss all my people i met here. my future is unknown. i have nobody. nobody wants to be my friend. its all over for me. idk wt a i do idk anymore idk anymor eidkajn;dflkajd;lkfja;sldka;lsdka;lsdka;lsdka;lsdka;sdlj</p>

<p>idk what i should say. idk idkdidkdkdklljaf;dslkfajlsad ive neve rbeen like this before.</p>

<p>i know i’ll get better, but he isn’t here now. just me.</p>]]></content><author><name>[&quot;seth&quot;, &quot;deathrow&quot;]</name></author><category term="chatting" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[the final days. i see a phsyciatrist at the end of the month. too far away. i hav eto move out of my room soon. i will miss all my people i met here. my future is unknown. i have nobody. nobody wants to be my friend. its all over for me. idk wt a i do idk anymore idk anymor eidkajn;dflkajd;lkfja;sldka;lsdka;lsdka;lsdka;lsdka;sdlj]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Back on the train tracks.</title><link href="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/back0ntrack/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Back on the train tracks." /><published>2024-11-18T20:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2024-11-18T20:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/back0ntrack</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/back0ntrack/"><![CDATA[<p>Should get back on track. It’s been a bit since I journaled stuff, especially within my Remarkable. I thought of getting the Remarkable Pro, not entirely sure though. I have the urge to buy stuff, though I probably shouldn’t. I actually just bought a Keychron keyboard and another monitor. Supposedly the Whoop 5.0 is coming out soon, around black friday. I sure hope so, because I want to buy that. Need to get back to watching Mr. Robot. I’ve seen it plenty of times, and plan on seeing it plenty more. On top of that, my money is going up yay. I am becoming super human. Bought a device which sends electric signals into my body to stimulate my muscles and such. Should relieve pain and soreness. I like this type of year. oh i got distracted and don’t remember what all i was say ing. Oakay then. Gonna play soem fallout</p>]]></content><author><name>[&quot;seth&quot;, &quot;deathrow&quot;]</name></author><category term="chatting" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Should get back on track. It’s been a bit since I journaled stuff, especially within my Remarkable. I thought of getting the Remarkable Pro, not entirely sure though. I have the urge to buy stuff, though I probably shouldn’t. I actually just bought a Keychron keyboard and another monitor. Supposedly the Whoop 5.0 is coming out soon, around black friday. I sure hope so, because I want to buy that. Need to get back to watching Mr. Robot. I’ve seen it plenty of times, and plan on seeing it plenty more. On top of that, my money is going up yay. I am becoming super human. Bought a device which sends electric signals into my body to stimulate my muscles and such. Should relieve pain and soreness. I like this type of year. oh i got distracted and don’t remember what all i was say ing. Oakay then. Gonna play soem fallout]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">IDK WHAT TO DO WITH MYSELF</title><link href="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/IDKWHATIMADO/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="IDK WHAT TO DO WITH MYSELF" /><published>2024-11-03T21:12:00-05:00</published><updated>2024-11-03T21:12:00-05:00</updated><id>https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/IDKWHATIMADO</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/IDKWHATIMADO/"><![CDATA[<p>Honestly, I do not know what I am going to do with myself… I missed my therapy appointment, and now I haven’t gone back. I think I need a break from college. I do not want to do this but, I think I have to. I’m not learning anything, nothing is hands-on, I frequently find myself not interested in the content as I already know it. I literally have known most of the things in my classes for years… It’s emberassing. I just haven’t been able to focus recently, or stay in the right headspace. I haven’t been journaling either. On top of that, haven’t really been eating. The only good thing that has improved is my sleep. Nothing interests me much. I’ve been dissociating like crazy. I just don’t know what else to do. I think I just need a break. It’s upsetting because my oldself would literally kill me for everything i’ve done. I haven’t seen him in a very long time… If i did, i would literally be dead. or bleeding out in the bathtub. I know he was strict, but it was worth it though. Maybe one day we’ll get him back, but he’s not here now is he. Nope. It’s hard to do anything. I have so much I want to do, I just can’t. and it even sucks that nobody IRL talks to me anymore. I’ve been getting extremely dizzy again, and I don’t know why. I need routine. But I get lonely with routine. Sometimes I just wanna do something. I wanna go to haunted houses with friends, I wanna go to rollercoasters and the movies… but I don’t have anybody to do those things with :c. I’ve tried meeting new people, just it’s almost impossible for me to make friends unless i’m literally forced to. IDK how to describe it. I used to be so much better. I know I shouldn’t reminisse on the past, but I used to be better than this. I literally,  I don’t know what I need. Every day is a blur, sometimes I just can’t remember anything thats happened, other times I get really confused. I wish I had a friend who lived with me. I just wanna hug someone sometimes but i cant. :c makes me sad.</p>]]></content><author><name>[&quot;seth&quot;, &quot;deathrow&quot;]</name></author><category term="chatting" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honestly, I do not know what I am going to do with myself… I missed my therapy appointment, and now I haven’t gone back. I think I need a break from college. I do not want to do this but, I think I have to. I’m not learning anything, nothing is hands-on, I frequently find myself not interested in the content as I already know it. I literally have known most of the things in my classes for years… It’s emberassing. I just haven’t been able to focus recently, or stay in the right headspace. I haven’t been journaling either. On top of that, haven’t really been eating. The only good thing that has improved is my sleep. Nothing interests me much. I’ve been dissociating like crazy. I just don’t know what else to do. I think I just need a break. It’s upsetting because my oldself would literally kill me for everything i’ve done. I haven’t seen him in a very long time… If i did, i would literally be dead. or bleeding out in the bathtub. I know he was strict, but it was worth it though. Maybe one day we’ll get him back, but he’s not here now is he. Nope. It’s hard to do anything. I have so much I want to do, I just can’t. and it even sucks that nobody IRL talks to me anymore. I’ve been getting extremely dizzy again, and I don’t know why. I need routine. But I get lonely with routine. Sometimes I just wanna do something. I wanna go to haunted houses with friends, I wanna go to rollercoasters and the movies… but I don’t have anybody to do those things with :c. I’ve tried meeting new people, just it’s almost impossible for me to make friends unless i’m literally forced to. IDK how to describe it. I used to be so much better. I know I shouldn’t reminisse on the past, but I used to be better than this. I literally, I don’t know what I need. Every day is a blur, sometimes I just can’t remember anything thats happened, other times I get really confused. I wish I had a friend who lived with me. I just wanna hug someone sometimes but i cant. :c makes me sad.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">feeling real wired</title><link href="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/wiredreally2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="feeling real wired" /><published>2024-10-10T15:41:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-10-10T15:41:00-04:00</updated><id>https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/wiredreally2</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/wiredreally2/"><![CDATA[<p>Feeling real wired right now.. Saw my therapist yesterday, guess it was good? I did have a good day last night.
I’ve been sedating myself every night at 20:00, doing such as given me a 90%+ recovery score. Drank a bunch of that special mushroom stuff today. Feeling real wired.</p>

<p>I feel like I have a billion things to do.. but im not sure how to describe it. Like i wanna do it, i just… ugh i feel like im done for the week. i don know.</p>

<p>been getting better tho!! new meds and whatnot which is a real plus!. hehehe.</p>

<p>Was gonna clean today.. or wait. Clean today, laundry tomorrow :)</p>]]></content><author><name>[&quot;seth&quot;, &quot;deathrow&quot;]</name></author><category term="chatting" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feeling real wired right now.. Saw my therapist yesterday, guess it was good? I did have a good day last night. I’ve been sedating myself every night at 20:00, doing such as given me a 90%+ recovery score. Drank a bunch of that special mushroom stuff today. Feeling real wired.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">everything loopy…</title><link href="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/loopysedated24/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="everything loopy…" /><published>2024-09-18T21:29:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-09-18T21:29:00-04:00</updated><id>https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/loopysedated24</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/loopysedated24/"><![CDATA[<p>i am sedated. i sedate myslef.</p>

<p>helllo vietnam. look at the that river</p>

<p>make a boy shiver.</p>

<p>ive been doing CTF and im very good at osint (i know), and crypto im up there toooo, ill hopefully get a full grasp of my skill sett.</p>

<p>today was a good day? id ont know maybe.</p>

<p>i fun last night, so this morning i awaken and i get food right? yeah. and i had cherry pepsi and prime with my stimulants, oh wait. hm. well i then took more of my med stimulants. hmm.</p>

<p>i did a bunch of studying? i got one assignment done.. yay..? boo..? idk but after i did laundry took a nap and went to the gym all at once. after that.. idk actually</p>

<p>small steps is good. study, nap and gym all in one day, woo. and i ate too. hmmm.</p>

<p>HMMMMM.</p>

<p>gonna be greattttt. right? yes!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</p>

<p>hi!!</p>

<p>i am cuteboi.</p>

<p>idk.</p>

<p>been workking on myh p osture too!!.</p>

<p>oh i also kinda cleaned my room tooo!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</p>

<p>and i showered!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!</p>

<p>before the gym and after.</p>

<p>i has very good feeling im going to be passed out sleepy tonight hehe.</p>

<p>only thing i need to improve on is sleep, maybe diet, and social skills (my health more important though, and well i havent had WAIT I HAVENT HAD PANIC ATTACKS IN A LONG TIME WOO!!!!!!!!. well within the past 24 hours but for me thats forever. You know.. taking sedatives at night… i took them wait not last night, but the night before.. They stay in my system for 100 hours. oh yeah. i mean i am prescribed them so duh. why WOULDN’T i take them..</p>

<p>oh i get very thirsty though. and every time i take them it reminds me of the way i feelt at the hospital when i tried to off myself. this is what 0 stress feels like. though my therapist had a good point, mixxing all these uppers and downers together… <em>IDK</em>.</p>

<p>hmm.</p>

<p>oh i’ve been forgetting to schedule doctors appointment for months now. uhhhh remind me tomorrow ? pls.</p>

<p>i’ve been improving a TON!.</p>

<p>i look amazing too.</p>

<p>have i found all i need?maybe. idk what that means.</p>

<p>being all by myslef in private room is amazing.</p>

<p>i ican sleep without panic attacks!lw woooo</p>

<p>from what i think and have seen, my only area on major improvement is social, BUT remember deathrow</p>

<p>everything is bettere by myself. right? yes maybe.</p>

<p>like IRL is better yes no social people IRL make me go way better. no anxiety, just back to the way I was. Just quite seth wearing all black in the back of the room. hood up? now wer’e getting frisky with the hood up..</p>

<p>i love wearing all black i really really really really love it.</p>

<p>black pants, black boots, black hoodie omg make me so wett.</p>

<p>hm what else. maybe better time management…?? idk maybe. i’ve been able to like study OH I HAVE TO TALK TO DOCTOR ABOUT MEDS.</p>

<p>ok remind me. i wis</p>

<p>sleep can always use improvement.</p>

<p>been journaling my thoughts too. well i’ve been doing that for.. wow years.. now that i think of it…. wow, it has been years.. idk im kinda scared to go back and read when i started.. feel like that’d bring back bad memories i dont want to remember.</p>

<p>ANYWAYS.god my vains are like. maybe thats what these pill do.</p>

<p>im very proud of myslef, ive been so much better!!! i feel so much confident and i dont feel insecure as much, maybe not at all? idk i cant think.</p>

<p>been exercising!!! (though i have to be careful been getting light headed and dizzy, i think too many stimulatns. oh there something wrong with my heart..? right? i don remember actually…) hmmm</p>

<p>i like the way i look, tall, lean, wide shoulders slim waist. im perfect. and pretty fit too.</p>

<p>woo woo woowooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo. ok ima get some wasser. caus emme is thirsy and ye i feel lOOky loops. oh it’s halloween soon!!</p>

<p>oh. i dont have anyone to do things with though :c i want to go to haunted house but nobody to go with.. :c now im sad. ok…</p>

<p>dont think of it. ok ok.</p>

<p>well thats all for now.</p>]]></content><author><name>[&quot;seth&quot;, &quot;sathe&quot;]</name></author><category term="chatting" /><category term="confusion" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[i am sedated. i sedate myslef.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Weekly Analysis 1</title><link href="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/WeeklyAnalysis1/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Weekly Analysis 1" /><published>2024-09-10T10:52:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-09-10T10:52:00-04:00</updated><id>https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/WeeklyAnalysis1</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/WeeklyAnalysis1/"><![CDATA[<h1 id="weekly-analysis-1">Weekly analysis 1.</h1>

<blockquote class="prompt-warning">
  <p>I’m sorry, I didn’t get a chance to finish this page. Doing all this is time consuming. - 09/17/2024 ~Seth</p>
</blockquote>

<p>I will be analyzing my habits, health and sharing various metrics.</p>

<p>To start off, let’s analyze my daily strain. This will help us identify potential anomalies and give us a better understanding of other metrics.</p>

<p><img src="../assets/img/weeklyanalysis1/9-10-strain.png" alt="" /></p>

<p>On the graph, we can see the day strain vs recovery.</p>

<p>What is interesting, <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">Wednesday</code> and <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">Saturday</code>, which have <em>~50%</em>, with <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">Wednesday</code> being a few percentages lower on the recovery scale - have..</p>

<p>Let’s analyze the <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">strain</code> first.</p>

<h2 id="strain">Strain</h2>

<p><em>Strain measures the cardiovascular and muscular load on the body throughout the day</em></p>

<p><strong>Strain Values</strong></p>

<p>Light (0-9) - Minimal stress put on the body, room for active recovery</p>

<p>Moderate (10-13) - Moderate stres on the body, generally good for maintaining fitness</p>

<p>High (14-17) - Increased stress and activity level, ideal for making fitness gains when training</p>

<p>All out (18-21) - Significant stress, often overreaching, likely very difficult to recover from the next day</p>

<h3 id="calculating-strain">Calculating Strain</h3>

<p>Strain is calculated on a logarithmic scale, measured from:</p>

<ul>
  <li>Heart Rate</li>
  <li>Duration &amp; Intensity</li>
</ul>

<p>First, let’s import the data into a table, creating rows <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">1-7</code> referencing the days of the week, staring with <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">sunday</code>.</p>

<table>
  <thead>
    <tr>
      <th>Strain (max 21)</th>
    </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td> </td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>4.3</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>4.2</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>9.9</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>7.2</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>5.8</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>12.6</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>6.7</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>

<p>Creating an initial histogram of <em>n=7</em></p>

<p><img src="../assets/img/weeklyanalysis1/strainhistogram.png" alt="" /></p>

<p>This doesn’t really give us the full picture, and is quite difficult to understand. We are just clustering here.</p>

<p>Instead, we can see the range within a boxplot:</p>

<p><img src="../assets/img/weeklyanalysis1/strainboxplot.png" alt="" /></p>

<p>We can see some valuable information such as:</p>

<p><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">Min: 4.2</code>
<code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">Q1: 4.3</code>
<code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">Median: 6.7</code>
<code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">Q3: 9.9</code>
<code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">Max 12.6</code></p>

<p>This lets us get a visual of the range. Theoretically the maximum amount of strain is 21.</p>

<p>Again, we can visualize this data:</p>

<p><img src="../assets/img/weeklyanalysis1/strainquantileplot.png" alt="" /></p>

<p>Now, we can add some other values into the mix. Recovery is on a scale of 100%.</p>

<p>Following the recovery scores, on the same rows of <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">1-7</code>,</p>

<table>
  <thead>
    <tr>
      <th style="text-align: left">Recovery Max (100%)</th>
    </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td style="text-align: left">6</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td style="text-align: left">87</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td style="text-align: left">97</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td style="text-align: left">44</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td style="text-align: left">64</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td style="text-align: left">79</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td style="text-align: left">51</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>

<p><img class="mermaid" src="https://mermaid.ink/svg/eyJjb2RlIjoieHljaGFydC1iZXRhXG50aXRsZSBcIlJlY292ZXJ5ICVcIlxueC1heGlzIFsxLCAyLCAzLCA0LCA1LCA2LCA3XVxueS1heGlzIFsxMCwgMjAsIDMwLCA0MCwgNTAsIDYwLCA3MCwgODAsIDkwLCAxMDBdXG5iYXIgWzYsIDg3LCA5NywgNDQsIDY0LCA3OSwgNTFdIiwibWVybWFpZCI6eyJ0aGVtZSI6ImRlZmF1bHQifX0" /></p>]]></content><author><name>[&quot;seth&quot;]</name></author><category term="quantified self" /><category term="health" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly analysis 1.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Everything is amazing.</title><link href="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/everythingisawesomehehehe/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Everything is amazing." /><published>2024-09-10T10:38:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-09-10T10:38:00-04:00</updated><id>https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/everythingisawesomehehehe</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/everythingisawesomehehehe/"><![CDATA[<p>Everything is awesome. I’m doing absolutely amazing. I was feelingg really really down yesterday, depressed, hopeless, starting to have a panic attack, then I recievevd an email stating my private room was ready. This is my time now. Time to fix my life. Time to be amazing. This girl I know goes to school with me. I guess we are friends ? I think she has severe anxiety like me, but I never talked about that cause I think she’s insecure about it me too. I wanna be really nice to her, she actually says hi to me when we walk by. I think I might be the only one she knows. It feels good to have someone to say hi to me.</p>

<p>Take my meds, feel amazing. Been seeing my therapist, that’s been super good too. Been trying to get better. We’ll see what happens. Finally getting out these years-worth of issue. I’ve actually been doing my school work on time too!!! Being alone in my room, I can really be myself, no distractions from others, no anxiety about people coming in.</p>

<p>Everything is reaelly great. and I love it. I feel great too! I know I can be better, I know I can be better with time-management and being impulsive. I haven’t been exercising as much but i’ve been getting myself into the right habits, right mental space before I go all in. I wanna slowly work to these things like getting up early and exercising. I don’t wanna force it all at once, I need to ease into it. Health-wise yes, I need to really exercise.</p>

<p>Been having a lot of confidence as well. I’ve learned, I talked honestly with a friend and she says that I give off an “akward” vibe. I understand. I know I act insecure. I’ve been more confident because of that. Trying to look my best.. I know hypervigilence can be a bitch. That probably makes me always look either insecure, anxious, shy, lonely, or up to no good. I don’t have these intentions, I just can’t control it.</p>

<p>Anyways, enough of the chatter. Time for some antalytical data. I’ll post this in a seperate document, to keep track. I’ll make a new tab, or something.</p>]]></content><author><name>[&quot;seth&quot;]</name></author><category term="chatting" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everything is awesome. I’m doing absolutely amazing. I was feelingg really really down yesterday, depressed, hopeless, starting to have a panic attack, then I recievevd an email stating my private room was ready. This is my time now. Time to fix my life. Time to be amazing. This girl I know goes to school with me. I guess we are friends ? I think she has severe anxiety like me, but I never talked about that cause I think she’s insecure about it me too. I wanna be really nice to her, she actually says hi to me when we walk by. I think I might be the only one she knows. It feels good to have someone to say hi to me.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Not sure</title><link href="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/notsurer21/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Not sure" /><published>2024-08-29T11:07:00-04:00</published><updated>2024-08-29T11:07:00-04:00</updated><id>https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/notsurer21</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://seth.rip/seth.rip/posts/notsurer21/"><![CDATA[<p>Not sure of anything. I want to do a lot, I think I need my meds fixed. I can’t sleep at night, every night I wake up drentched in sweat. I’ve been making a lot of really really good progress, but I know I can be like even better. Like I know I can be super better better. Like even more so. I can wake up earlier, I can exercise more, I can study more, I can work on my projects more. I can improve <em>more</em>. I’m so close. I just need a little help.</p>]]></content><author><name>[&quot;sathe&quot;]</name></author><category term="chatting" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not sure of anything. I want to do a lot, I think I need my meds fixed. I can’t sleep at night, every night I wake up drentched in sweat. I’ve been making a lot of really really good progress, but I know I can be like even better. Like I know I can be super better better. Like even more so. I can wake up earlier, I can exercise more, I can study more, I can work on my projects more. I can improve more. I’m so close. I just need a little help.]]></summary></entry></feed>